I've got this!
Well, that's the end of that.
All teams retreat.
Grid 1-9's too hot.
We could have killed them
all if we stuck with it.
You sure you want to end
the day like this, boss?
That team's all over the place.
Fighting them won't
help with our training.
We have a big mission coming
up, and we need to stay sharp.
Let's go.
Mr.
Miller, the people from the NSA are here.
Send them in, please.
Mr. Miller,
we'd like to retain the services of GloGen
Defense Systems for a top-secret mission.
What is the nature of the mission?
To acquire a piece of tech
called Soul Translation.
I'm not familiar with what that is.
A Japanese company called
Wrath developed it.
It's a machine capable
of analyzing a soul.
A human soul?
That's hard to believe.
Yes, well, it's been verified.
With this soul translation tech,
not only can Wrath scan and
read a soul, they can clone it.
The project is codenamed ALICE,
and its goal is to develop an artificial
soul to pilot military drones.
That kind of tech would disrupt
the balance of power in East Asia.
Needless to say, the U .S.
is concerned and wants to
keep that from happening.
Understandable.
Please go on.
What are the specifics of the mission?
There's a mega-float moored
near the Izu Islands.
It's called the Ocean Turtle.
We need you to infiltrate the facility,
secure the soul translation
tech, and bring it back.
So you want to raid a Japanese
vessel, one of our allies?
We have a contact inside the JSDF.
They'll be sure to leave the
window open for you on the day.
Use whatever methods you want.
Just keep in mind this is off the books.
You won't get any support from the U .S.
if you get caught.
All right, then.
I'll assemble a team and
lead this mission myself.
Alice, your soul will be
sweet, maybe the sweetest yet.
Thank you.
One one one thing.
That's what I wanted to do.
I didn't catch my opponent in my hand.
I don't want to be a Bear.
I didn't catch my opponent, I knew.
I would love to be single of the failures.
I am sure I can experience it.
I'm yeah.
I am strong enough.
Can I make it easy for me?
I'm strong enough.
I believe that I have a strong
strength with my strength.
I could try and crack it
with the laptop we brought,
but you'd die of old age before I got in.
They boned us, and there's
nothing I can do about it.
That ain't all you said,
you four-eyed scumbag.
You said we wouldn't be stuck like this
if we weren't so slow getting in here.
So what if I did?
I was just pointing out the faxes.
Next time, instead of
waiting for the all-clear,
you're coming up front with us, you pussy.
Enough.
You boys better cool down.
This isn't the time to start
pointing fingers at each other.
We have to figure out how
to deal with the situation.
Come on, bro.
Let me put this worm in his place.
I said stand down.
Everyone did what they were supposed to.
Aside from Gary getting winged
by a round, the team's intact.
And now that we're in the control room,
we're exactly where we need
to be to get this done.
Get what done?
If we can't get access to the system, then
we can't get what we came here to get.
The schematic said everything's automated,
and the light cube cluster
things behind a wall of steel.
Right.
So all we have to do now is figure
out a way to breach that wall.
Yeah, well, the SDF agents on board
ain't gonna hide in their holes forever.
And when that ship outside
figures out what's what,
we'll be up to our ass in soldiers.
The client told me they have a
special relationship with the JSDF.
They assured me we'd have a Hero
window before the ship rolled in.
Ooh, espionage.
That's way better than a
boring old smash-and-grab.
Alright, let's go over the situation.
We stormed the facility 40 minutes ago.
Right now, it's 1447 local time.
We're standing in the main
control room of the Ocean Turtle.
We've been locked out of the system,
and we were unable to capture any
Wrath staff to help us unlock it.
A minor setback, not the end of the world.
Our new objective is to infiltrate the
sub-control room and try from there.
Well, Brig, do you think it's possible
to cut through the bulkhead door?
Not with the kind of gear we brought.
It's made out of some kind of
rock-hard composite material.
If we gotta be out of here in 24,
the portable saw ain't enough.
We need something bigger and sharper.
Alright.
Hans, can we use C4 to blow it?
Sure, but I wouldn't recommend it.
The chamber with the light cube cluster is
supposed to be on the other
side of the wall there.
If we blow the door, we'd risk damaging
the chamber and everything in it.
Hmm.
Alright,
somehow we have to find one light cube
in a vault of thousands and retrieve it.
We have the cube's ID.
As long as we have a working console, we
can eject it along with its interface.
Piece of cake.
Thank God we brought Senior
Dork along for the ride.
All that BS about hacking the Pentagon.
If you were really that good you would
have had this system open by now.
Listen to the super
soldier up to now the only
combat you've seen's been
the virtual kind Haas.
God damn nerd!
Do you want to go back empty-handed and
instead of a big fat bonus get laughed at?
Hell no
And how about you?
Are you gonna let some amateur
programmers lock you out?
No.
Then think, dammit.
Come up with a way to get in and prove
you got more than oatmeal in your skulls.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
The pressurized bulkhead leading to the
Light Cube cluster can't be breached.
We have to find some other
way to access it from here.
What you got?
Admin privileges can't unlock the system.
All I can do is bring
up a visual of the world
so we can see what all
the Fluk lights are doing.
Basically, watch them living their lives
in their little fairy tale kingdom.
Goblins?
You know your fantasy tropes, Captain.
They seem kind of big for regular goblins.
Yeah, those things are hop goblins.
Critter. Hmm, yeah?
Are those creatures part
of the system, like NPCs?
Mama.
Not according to what I'm seeing.
Check it out.
They all got their own light cube designation,
which means they're in the cluster.
Those things all have souls.
You're kidding.
Those hobgoblins have human souls?
Same as us?
Yo, check out what the
other light cubes got.
Like, maybe they're all filled
with goblin and orc souls, too.
Maybe Alice is one.
Would you chill?
Look at the screen.
The underworld is split into the human
empire where, you know, humans live.
And surrounding that, on the
other side of the mountains,
is the dark territory
where the monsters are.
With a name like Alice, I'm pretty
sure she's both a she and human.
The problem is, the human part
is so big and filled with people,
we'll never find her like this.
Not sitting out here, that's for sure.
But in there we could.
If they got a civilization, they can talk.
So just drop me in and I can
ask around till I find her.
Good idea.
For a dumbass.
You little bastard!
Stop and think.
There's tens of thousands of
people living in the Human Empire.
It's huge and you're just one person.
You can't ask him.
Free one?
Unless...
you're someone with
some clout. Good point.
The researchers must have special
accounts they could use to log in there.
It's a safe bet those
accounts would be a higher
level than the average
citizen isn't that right,
critter?
Yeah, boss exactly!
Out of all the ranks and classes the wrath
peeps had to set aside
a few to use that way.
They could monitor and
tweak the world from inside.
Uh-huh, now we're talking.
Hey, how about if I log in as a general
or president or something like that?
I'd give the order to find Alice and
let the grunts do the work Oh, my God.
Now that I hear you say it, I'm not
so sure I'm a fan of the idea anymore.
Balls.
They got all these high-level accounts
locked down as tight as the system.
If we dive into the Human Empire, it's
gonna be as a plain old low-level person.
Damn it.
So much for that idea.
No. Try again.
But this time, search for any high-level
accounts outside the Human Empire.
Outside it?
Okay, but the chances of Alice being
in Monsterland is close to nil.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
But if all that separates the two regions
are mountains, they can be crossed.
Yeah, that's why you're in charge.
Always thinking outside the box.
I can see it now.
I'll dive in as a boss monster
and leader raid on the humans.
I'd be down with that.
Look, I think I found a couple contenders.
No password required
gents specs look good this
one's classified as a
dark knight so edgy and
His object control levels
at 70 he's a badass to
the bone sweet right up
my alley yo i got dibs on
The dark knight i found
another account that we
can access well that's
weird there's no rank and
it Doesn't have a level
either no durability system
control authority the
only setting is its name
Emperor Vector hell yeah
that guy's the king of
the monster world changed
my mind i'll be him no
I'll use that account all
right bro you're the emperor
and i'm cool being a dark
knight Let's get this show on
the road i want to chop some
fools with my sword come on
four eyes what Do we gotta
do to log in speak up critter
something's obviously
bothering you maybe i'm just
being Overcautious but i keep
seeing the same term pop up
again and again in these
logs it might not Affect our
op but still go on what is
this term the final load test
How do i put this as far as kirito's real
world condition it's
like i said before Things
aren't looking too good for him the only
thing that gives me hope
is he's still Logged
into the underworld that's good see even
though his self-image is damaged his Flux
light still active and
receiving stimuli so
there's a chance his
neural network can heal
I was thinking, his guilt over losing his
friends is what damaged his soul, right?
What if, and it's a big what
if, what if someone forgave him?
That might help.
Send me. I'll go.
Asuna.
I'll go.
Log me into the underworld.
I want to tell him that
he did all he could that
it's okay that after
all the pain and sadness
I Know he suffered in
the end he did the best
he could all right we have
another STL we can use
But the underworld's at
a critical stage it's
not exactly stable right
now it's scheduled to
enter The final load test
soon the last phase of
the experiment final load
test what happens then
The eastern gate separates
the human empire from
the dark territory once
its durability Level hits
zero the monsters will
invade the human side if
the humans were able to
build up Their defenses
in time they could drive
the monsters back to
their side but now it's
up in The air kirito
pretty much destroyed the
axiom church the ruling
body there so who knows
what Will happen now at
this point having someone
dive in there might
be the best course of
action for all Our concerns
once the invasion begins
there's no telling how
chaotic the underworld
will get And there's a
good chance alice could
be killed but if we send
someone in using a high
level account They could
find Alice and have the
power to keep her safe
long enough to get her
to the World End's altar.
Then, using the terminal there, they can
eject her light cube to this control room.
Ah, so that's why you told Kirito
to take her there, to eject her.
He'd have gotten her there
by now, if he were able to.
You heard what he said.
She was right there with him.
Time there's accelerated, so
by now months have passed.
Do you think there's a chance
they're still together?
Even now?
I'd say it's a good bet they are.
And personally, I think if anyone's
gonna dive in, it should be Asuna.
She's our best hope at
breaking through to Kirito.
Plus, she's got the combat skills to
protect Alice and get her to the terminal.
You don't need to convince me about that.
All right, let's find her a
high-level account to dive in with.
Sure thing.
I got tons of options.
A knight, a general, a noble, whatever
you pick's gonna have high stats, Asuna.
Wait, I just thought of something.
What is it?
What about the people in main con?
If they're here for Alice, maybe
they've got the same idea we do.
Yeah, maybe.
There's two STLs over there
they can use. Thing is,
the passwords I set for the
high-level accounts are tough,
and they won't have time to crack them.
If they dive in, they can
only go as a level one person.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Nah, it's nothing.
Are you ready for this?
Yeah, ready as I'll ever be.
I don't know.
Your soul…
will be so sweet.
Jeez, not him again.
Asuna.
Hi, Sinon.
I have to tell you and the
others something important.
Could you please log into ALO right away?
It's risky, but there's a chance
Daddy's Fluchtlight can be repaired.
So Mommy dove into the
Underworld to save him.
I hope she can.
What if she can't?
Would you guys stop worrying?
Kirito's always pulled through before.
This sucks.
I can't stand that
they're stuck out there.
And those hijackers.
What if they figure
out how to get to them?
There's gotta be something we can
do, except sit around and wait.
They're safe for now.
But be ready.
If worse comes to worse, I'll
be calling on you for help.
Fasten your seatbelts, gents.
Thank you for seeing me, my lord.
I, Lipia Zankale, bring news. Very good.
Take a seat.
Thank you, my lord.
Don't be so formal.
It's just us here.
Yes, I know.
But officially, I'm still on duty.
Have it your way.
You were familiar warned
of an impending emergency.
Is it that serious?
Yes, quite serious.
The pontifex of the Axiom Church is dead.
That immortal being? Yes.
I too found it hard to believe,
so I spent the past week confirming it.
I see.
Perfect.
I'm sorry, perfect for... For peace.
Peace for all.
Is that still possible?
Do you honestly believe that, my lord?
Whether it's possible or not, it
must be achieved, no matter what.
But, my lord, you would first have to
convince the other nine in the council, and,
well,
would the Order of Integrity Knights even
entertain peace negotiations with us? Yes.
I believe the Integrity
Knights would be interested.
If the Pontifex is dead, then I'd
wager old man Bercouli is in command.
now.
I can't stand him, but he is reasonable.
I hate to say this,
but the only thing that
could get in the way of peace
talks would be our Council of Ten.
Not all, just four
of them.
They will have to die.
Lord, that's too risky.
You could handle the Goblin Chiefs
and the Orc Chief. However...
The head of the Dark Mages Guild
would be difficult, I know.
She hopes to find the Secret to
administrators immortality and one day become
Empress peace would get in the way of her
ambitions precisely that is why you cannot
take the chance my lord as I said the
goblin and orc chiefs are no match for you
but she is diabolical I can't imagine what
kind of evil spell she has up her sleeve?
Listen, Lippia, how long
have you and I been together?
Uh, well, um, since I turned 21, I think.
So, four years now?
That long, really?
Forgive me.
I made you wait far too long.
It's not fair.
I was thinking,
maybe now we could, you know,
make it official and
become husband and wife.
Lord. I know.
I wish I were younger, too.
emergency it's an emergency
come to the throne
room the chain that seals
the door is trembling
Hmph.